Number 0011, please proceed to Window 3.
She turned herself in.
When did that happen?
Last night, after work.
She confessed to everything.
You bet.
Time, location, motive.
The old lady didn't hide a thing.
Then how does this count?
What? How does what count?
I mean, does this count as me solving the case?
Well, what do you think?
She turned herself in.
How could it count as you solving it?
At most, you just found some clues.
Finding clues should count for something, right?
Yunsheng, you're obsessed with getting credit.
This case is a bit special.
Commissar Tan, you're here.
Have you had breakfast?
I have. Thank you, Commissar Tan.
You're welcome.
Commissar Tan, you're here.
Want some breakfast?
I've had some. Thank you.
Morning, Commissar Tan.
Morning, morning.
I bought some spiced boiled eggs.
Here, hand them out to everyone.
Thank you, Commissar Tan. Thanks, Commissar.
You're welcome, you're welcome.
What... what happened to your legs?
Were you on a mission?
Don't ask.
My legs and butt don't feel like my own.
The training was too intense.
I overdid it.
You need to take it easy.
You're a commissar, no need to push so hard.
It's not like I want to.
The chief is in his dorm.
Spiced eggs, have some.
Thank you, thank you.
Morning, Commissar Tan.
Who can eat all of this?
Here, this is for everyone.
Spiced boiled eggs.
Mini fried dough.
Jianbing.
Millet porridge.
Sesame balls.
No steamed buns.
There's something for everyone.
I've already had breakfast.
You're not having any?
Well, we can't let it go to waste.
My legs and butt don't feel like my own.
Tan Yan, about us...
We... we're not talking about us today.
We're talking about work.
What work?
About
Wang Yunsheng.
Haven't we already talked about this?
If he wants to leave, I won't stop him.
I heard about Dai Mingming's case.
I wanted to talk to you about it.
Talk about what?
Dai Mingming and his mother.
It was Wang Yunsheng
who saved them.
The clues
were also from him.
Why are you excluding him now?
How much do you know about this case?
A fair amount.
A terminally ill elderly mother
with an intellectually disabled son.
Feared her son couldn't survive alone,
so she wanted to die with him.
It sounds heartbreaking.
Of course,
Chief Ji must have more details.
Dai Mingming's mom turned herself in.
This case
was originally
one where no one pressed charges.
Hard to tell if it was suicide or murder.
So I had Wang Yunsheng assist Li Zhi.
We couldn't jump to conclusions.
But Wang Yunsheng acted on his own.
He brought Dai Mingming to the station.
Though you're off the front lines now,
you're still a veteran cop.
In this kind of situation,
what do you think would happen?
We'd have to investigate it to the end.
So do you still think
that me excluding Wang Yunsheng
is a problem?
When it comes to experience in this area,
Wang Yunsheng is severely lacking.
But he is the one who saved them.
I think this kid
can endure hardship,
has drive,
and has great enthusiasm for police work.
That's very valuable.
He just lacks experience.
Experience needs to be accumulated.
Which requires us leaders
to give him opportunities.
It's hard for an auxiliary to go regular.
He'll get all the credit he deserves.
I'll give him the chances he deserves.
There's one more thing you don't know.
He's actually quite like you in this.
In what way?
Eager for quick success.
The sesame balls lack filling today.
That old guy must've made them, look.
Do you need anything else?
If not, I'm going to change clothes.
Okay, go ahead.
I'll clean this up for you.
No need.
Just go.
I'll close the door for you.
Commissar Tan
Tomorrow we rappel at the fire station.
Are you going?
Yeah, I'm going.
That's great!
Eight stories. Not too high, but very fun.
You should give it a try.
Lu Xiao,
stop trying to get people hurt.
Shoo, shoo. Stay away, stay away.
Commissar Tan, don't listen to him.
Rappelling is not like running.
Man, it's not easy to pick up.
You might end up flipping over.
Boss, you underestimate Commissar Tan.
He kept up with the ten-kilometer run.
He'll learn it in a couple of tries.
How is that the same thing?
I wasn't planning on trying it.
Mainly just to observe and learn.
You guys do it.
Done showering, Commissar.
Done showering.
Good night, good night.
Why aren't you pushing yourself anymore?
Just lying flat, you know.
What's his time?
Next group, let's go.
Lu Xiao.
Set a new standard.
Set an example for everyone.
Just watch, boss.
What's the time?
Captain Liao, a new record?
Still a bit short.
Lu Xiao!
You broke the record!
Faster by 0.8 seconds.
Not bad.
Lu Xiao!
Don't let it get to your head.
This is a new starting point.
This is the new standard for the team.
Do you hear me?
Yes, sir!
At ease.
Alright, take a 15-minute break.
While we're taking a break,
let's have a quick meeting.
You guys really opened my eyes.
Lu Xiao,
you're really fast.
You're light on your feet.
I even suspect you stomped that wall
and made it a few centimeters shorter.
Liu Lang, what you just said,
about reaching a new starting point,
was well said.
It pushed our goal a big step forward.
Exactly.
Improving by 0.8 seconds isn't easy.
With a benchmark like you on the team,
how could this team
not be motivated to improve?
Bai Jiani,
the only female officer on our SWAT team.
Your rappelling was incredibly swift.
Even swifter
than the moves
by our foreign counterparts
I've seen in documentaries.
Outstanding.
Thank you, Commissar.
Our SWAT team's
current combat effectiveness
couldn't have been achieved
without everyone's hard work.
Improving team quality to excellence...
that is what makes us truly formidable.
I mean every word I say.
I also hope everyone speaks their minds.
No matter what problems,
difficulties,
or differing opinions you have,
bring them up boldly.
Lu Xiao, say a few words.
I think this training ground is great.
Training here helped me break the record.
But our SWAT team doesn't have one.
Right.
We don't have one.
But we have an intense training regimen.
Without intense training,
could you have broken the record?
If it's just about the facility,
why didn't they break the record?
Judging from your performance,
relying solely on physical training
is no longer enough to meet
the demands of future challenges.
The team's overall quality,
especially ideological discipline,
in my opinion,
is more important than physical fitness.
Commissar,
how do we discipline our minds?
Well, here's what I think.
While we strengthen our bodies,
we should elevate our minds.
We'll resume the weekly meetings
and ideological classes.
Submit a reflection report every 3 days.
Share takeaways from life and training.
You can even write about your frustrations.
I'll review and comment on every one.
And grade them, too.
One every three days, ten a month.
Harder than at the Police University.
It's not demanding.
Come on, next item, climbing!
Fall in!
Boss.
What's Old Tan playing at?
You don't get it?
Just the new boss making his mark.
Hurry up.
Can you keep it down?
You totally ruined my train of thought.
Let me tell you.
I get it now.
I completely get it.
It's not that I can't write it.
I just don't want to.
Then don't write it.
Wrong.
Not only am I going to write it,
I'm going to make it brilliant.
My self-reflection report.
I thought you'd had some huge revelation.
Found it.
Here's another one. Want it?
No.
Sent it to your phone.
For when you finally 'get it,'
it'll come in handy.
Not bad, rookie.
Scribbling away, huh?
Such talent.
Way better than your boss.
Stop acting. Give it here, I'll do it.
Thanks.
Just four words?
No wonder you're better than me.
I'm telling you,
I'm definitely not slacking off.
It's mainly because this weekend,
I promised my wife
to take the kids out to play.
Are you hungry? I'll go buy you some food.
Not hungry.
I mean, what is Commissar Tan thinking?
What's the use of writing this stuff?
Whether it's useful doesn't matter.
What you write doesn't matter either.
The key is
whether you listen to him
and submit the report on time.
Got it.
A compliance test.
Then I'll just write whatever.
You can write whatever,
but definitely don't half-ass my copy.
Will Captain Liao write it?
Take a guess.
I really can't write this thing of yours.
Don't know how?
I'll help you.
201.
Writing your ideological report is useless.
If you think
this training of mine
is also useless,
you don't have to participate.
I think this training method of yours
is very useful.
Didn't I say it this afternoon?
Right now, in terms of fitness and...
and skills,
we're doing very well.
It's just that this ideological work,
we need to take it seriously.
You've done over 210 in this set.
I really can't write it.
Your muscles...
they're really popping. Popping.
These triceps.
These... these biceps.
This definition is so beautiful.
You should take the lead.
The whole team is watching you.
Please cooperate with my work.
How much willpower would it take...
Could I... could I build, in half a year,
definition like yours?
No.
Falsification.
It's a reference.
The whole team is watching me too.
You have high awareness.
Your ideology has no issues.
But that doesn't mean others don't.
Otherwise, why would the leaders...
have me focus on ideological work?
Alright.
It's just the two of us in this room.
We're both in the SWAT team.
If you really want everyone to respect you,
then stop doing superficial work.
Do something practical.
Tell me, what's practical?
Our SWAT team...
lacks facilities and equipment.
We even borrow the firehouse to rappel.
What? Rap...
Rappel training.
Rappelling.
So these things are very important now.
Very important.
I've noted it all down.
Captain Liao,
I must emphasize...
No, I have to correct you on this.
Ideological work is not
optional.
It's a top priority.
You can look down on me,
but you can't look down on my work.
This is very serious.
Commissar Tan,
you don't
seem like you're here to pad your resume.
Don't ask for trouble here for nothing.
Why are you asking for trouble here?
I sent you to the SWAT team to fix them.
Don't turn into a virus yourself.
If you still rely on old superficial tricks
to just go through the motions here,
I can't guarantee
you'll be able to come back in two years.
Commissar Tan.
What are you doing?
I can tidy up myself.
I'm not tidying up for you.
We're roommates from now on.
I'm moving in tonight.
Do you normally snore?
I don't know.
I'll move out right now.
Don't want to live with your Commissar?
No desire to advance?
Relax.
At work,
we are superior and subordinate.
But back in the dorm,
we're just roommates.
If you want to advance,
stick close to me.
Then I'll take the top bunk.
There's no rank in the dorm!
I just like sleeping on the top bunk.
Really.
He moved into Wang Yunsheng's room.
He just had me move a desk for him.
Are you two alright?
We're fine.
Did he say anything to you?
Just a few words.
Said he wants to take root at the base.
And eat and live with the regular guys.
To experience what they feel firsthand.
Putting on a show again.
Why overthink it?
Who cares if it's a show?
Just remember,
as long as he doesn't delay our training,
we're good.
Two years
will pass in a flash.
What are you doing?
Picking up a package.
Wait a minute.
Captain Liao.
Up so late?
Bought a toy for Naonao.
Where's Naonao?
Asleep.
He's already asleep.
Doesn't he like airplanes?
I bought one for him.
Thanks, Captain Liao. Very thoughtful.
Don't mention it.
Tom Hardy?
It's my screen name.
Tom Hardy, I know him.
That British actor, right?
He has a very unique look.
Right.
Venom.
Yes, yes, that's him!
Why pick that name?
They all say we look quite alike.
You do look a bit alike.
Right?
Alright then, I'll go back and rest.
Thanks, Tom Hardy.
Tom Hardy.
How's the progress on Dai Mingming's case?
It's been transferred to CID.
Mingming's mom is in the detention center.
Mingming's at the welfare home for now.
Now we're just waiting for the trial.
Chief Ji has been in a bad mood lately.
Chief Ji isn't handling this anymore.
I heard from Li Zhi
that Chief Ji will visit the city bureau
next week to report on Dai Mingming's case.
What day is he going?
Monday.
He should go right after his shift starts.
This case wasn't supposed to get this far.
It's my fault I brought Mingming here.
Commissar Tan,
have I completely disappointed Chief Ji?
Yunsheng, do you want to change
how Chief Ji sees you?
I do.
I know a way.
Come in.
Commissar Tan.
Xiao Lu, need something?
I need to ask for leave.
My mom is sick.
Which hospital?
She's in Lvteng.
Is it serious?
It's not serious.
It's just I'm from a single-parent family,
and I'm an only child.
Right, that's a tricky situation.
I'll have the admin staff buy some things
and visit your mom on behalf of the unit.
No need for the trouble.
I'll be quick.
I finished my report. Please take a look.
Alright.
The writing is fluent.
The logic is clear.
Good.
What a perfect template.
Then... did I pass, Commissar Tan?
Xiao Lu.
I'm sure that
a top Police University student like you
can definitely write one
that's even better than this template.
Commissar Tan, what about my leave?
I'll approve it after you rewrite it.
Thank you, Commissar Tan.
I'm heading to the city bureau
for a meeting.
Hurry up. Don't delay visiting your mom.
Where did the boss go?
To a meeting at the city bureau.
He didn't approve your leave, did he?
He did.
He did?
Once I finish writing.
Writing what?
I got busted.
Then mine is probably doomed too.
Yours is fine.
I copied the one from 2018.
Yours is from 2017.
He won't remember.
What nonsense is that? Come back here!
Rewrite it. Hurry up.
So annoying.
Commissar Tan.
Commissar Tan, long time no see.
Long time no see.
Ji Min.
You're going to see Chief Guo, aren't you?
I heard from Wang Yunsheng.
I'll go with you.
Tan Yan, I appreciate your kindness.
You can't help with this.
Ji Min.
Let me show you a video.
Over the weekend, Wang Yunsheng and I
tracked down Dai Yumei's neighbors.
Mom left me with Aunt Dai when she worked.
Aunt Dai always used to say,
taking care of one is the same
as taking care of two.
Don't worry.
I sincerely hope the government
considers Dai Yumei turning herself in
and be lenient with her.
You two, one from the local station,
one from the SWAT team.
What kind of duo is this?
It's just a coincidence.
A coincidence?
Before transferring to the local station,
he was in our SWAT detachment.
This is also his first case.
As his political commissar,
it's my duty to look out for him.
Chief Guo.
Sentencing Dai Yumei is easy.
But she has late-stage cancer.
Punishing her holds no real significance.
Plus, Dai Mingming is a special needs kid.
If it weren't for Dai Yumei,
he couldn't take care of himself at all.
There's a great saying.
It says the law
doesn't just have
a cold side.
It has a warm side too.
Well said, right?
Very well.
How is this a coincidence?
You planned this, singing the same tune.
We really didn't plan this.
Alright, I understand the case now.
I have to say, it is quite special.
I'll send the video to you.
What?
Do you two have any other coincidences?
No. I have a meeting next.
No.
Goodbye, Chief.
Chief, look at me.
Haven't I lost a lot of weight?
I can't tell.
My belt is even looser.
I've been working out.
You need to keep at it.
Let's go.
Alright, Chief Guo, we're heading out.
Thank you, Chief Guo.
This couple...
What are they playing at?
I didn't act on my own this time, did I?
Barely.
But this time, I really want to thank you.
Don't mention it.
I'm thanking you for Mingming and his mom.
Time to eat. Let's get some food together.
I've got time.
Last time they all thought we had a fight.
Are you going?
Why wouldn't I?
Just wait.
They aren't here yet.
So unreliable.
Who's unreliable?
We're here, we're here.
Director Tan.
Chief Ji.
Take a seat, take a seat.
What's going on?
You two came together?
Acting just like a married couple.
We are a married couple, isn't it normal?
It's normal.
It's just that...
...before this,
...right?
Either one arrives just before...
...or just after the other.
Now that you're acting normal...
...it actually seems abnormal.
Are those two coming?
They're unreliable, I told you.
Are they coming or not?
You better hurry up.
Let's eat while we wait.
Let's eat then.
Eat, eat, eat.
We'll eat while we wait.
Don't burn your hands.
I read this issue of the police magazine.
That big photo of you looks good.
You look like a celebrity.
Don't, don't bring it up.
The leadership chewed me out.
They said I infected...
...the entire SWAT detachment.
Hurry and help me think of a way.
How to assert authority on the SWAT team.
What way can I think of for you?
Isn't asserting authority your forte?
The key isn't asserting authority.
It's winning them over.
Those are two different things.
Look at him.
Just look at what Old Ji said.
He always hits the nail on the head.
No, what's going on with you?
Your previous trick...
...of playing the big boss didn't work?
It's not working anymore.
The leaders called me a...
...virus.
Do you think it's working?
You really are a virus.
So tonight...
I need you guys to help me brainstorm.
Think of a way.
Are they coming? Call and hurry them up.
We're all here.
Coming, coming, we're here.
You better hurry up.
So unreliable.
Way too unreliable.
What happened?
We went to line up.
Lined up to buy some braised meat.
Come on, try some.
Here, here, take this.
You two look pretty put together today.
What do you mean put together? Clothes?
No, you two really are put together today.
Right?
They're a married couple.
What's wrong with being put together?
Just stop talking.
I hate hearing you talk.
It's so annoying.
What's the occasion today?
Is there some good news to celebrate?
Such a feast.
Didn't you read the police magazine?
Old Tan is front and center.
Really?
Of course.
You saw it?
I saw it.
Did you?
Don't mention this front and center thing.
Let me tell you,
Old Tan is finished.
What happened to you?
He can't establish his authority.
He wants to assert authority on the team,
but he can't.
He wants us to think of something.
S-SWAT team...
Isn't that simple?
You... when you go to the SWAT team,
you can't lower yourself to their level.
You have to hold your head high.
You need to make them look up to you.
But honestly,
those SWAT boys,
sometimes,
you need a little whip behind them.
You have to whip them.
I did. I whipped them plenty.
It doesn't work.
We gotta serve them something tough.
Think of a way.
What way can we think of?
We... we can go show our support for you.
Forget it, what support?
What?
With Liao Bufan's terrible temper,
would he show any of us respect?
Would he respect you?
Hey, hey, don't say 'us'.
It has nothing to do with us.
What's the main reason here?
You get no respect.
Get outta here.
I really hate hearing you talk.
Do I need his respect?
He's just so simple-minded every day...
and completely unreasonable.
Right?
Exactly.
Right now, that Liao kid
has made a mess of the SWAT detachment.
His personal style is too strong.
Tough to handle, very tough.
Let me remind you, Old Tan.
You bring this anxiety upon yourself.
Yesterday it was Zhao Guohua.
Today it's Liao Bufan.
And tomorrow?
Zhao Guohua.
Just pick it up.
Chief Zhao.
I heard them say
you're at the Little Courtyard Farmhouse?
I'm... I'm here too.
You're at the Little Courtyard too?
Wait, where are you?
Which room?
I'm right here.
Chief Zhao, Chief Zhao.
Captain Zhang.
Captain Na.
Commissar Tan.
Sister-in-law.
You guys are really here.
That's great.
Smooth sailing, smooth sailing.
Well,
have a seat.
I... I won't. I've been sitting all day.
Today... It's such a coincidence today.
I'm right next door. Right next door.
And their boss told me
that you were here.
I said, 'Really?'
Because who have I been trying to invite?
I've been trying to invite Captain Na.
Right.
I've kept in touch with Captain Na.
But you know how it is at work.
Work is just too busy.
Yeah.
Running into you here, what a coincidence.
Commissar Tan,
have you
moved into the SWAT base now?
I have moved into the SWAT base.
Putting duty before family.
Eating, sleeping, and training together.
It's a special period.
My family understands and supports it.
Since I just arrived at the SWAT base,
if I want to win them over, I have to
lead by example.
Indeed, indeed.
Because last time, so coincidentally,
I went to the SWAT base and saw him
running behind the team.
Indeed.
Grab some chopsticks and have a bite.
How about this, how about this.
I'll use this
tea.
Let me pour it, let me pour it.
Thank you, Commissar Tan.
I'll substitute tea for liquor.
So,
I'll
raise a glass to everyone.
Unload everything.
Careful not to damage anything.
Ma'am.
Naonao, go play in your room.
What's the meaning of this?
These are the things you use at home.
Mr. Lu told me to bring them over to you.
No need. Take them back.
Please don't make this hard for me.
You know Mr. Lu's temper.
If you don't accept them,
he'll make me deliver them every day.
This is a gift from Mr. Lu.
It's this year's latest model.
He said
he hasn't forgotten what he promised you.
By the way, Ma'am.
We rented a place right across the street.
We figured if anything happens at the shop,
we'd be close by to help out.
Mr. Lu also left instructions.
Whatever you'd like to eat from now on,
three meals a day,
we'll make it and deliver it to you.
Not necessary.
The SWAT team is right across the street.
I'm warning you,
don't try anything.
We just rented a place across the street.
Like the SWAT team can do anything.
Alright, Ma'am.
I'll leave you to it.
Call me anytime if you need anything.
Mom.
Where's Lu Xiao?
He's on leave.
His mom is sick.
Tonight's mission: patrol and inspect.
Mingliu Club.
Heavy foot traffic.
It's our key focus.
But I can't guarantee
that all incoming guests are clean.
A 2,000-word self-criticism.
A bureau-wide reprimand.
Hurry up and apologize.
What did I do wrong?
Captain Liao, something's up with Naonao.
Can you hear Mommy?
Can you hear me?